  {
    "questions_and_answers": [
      {
        "question": "What is the Twinning Program offered by Nitte (Deemed to be University) in collaboration with Penn State University, Harrisburg?",
        "answer": "It allows students of BTech in Computer Science Engineering at Nitte Mahalinga Adyanthaya Memorial Institute of Technology (NMAMIT) to complete part of their study at Penn State University (PSU), Harrisburg. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/DualDegree.php"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of university is Pennsylvania State University (PSU)?",
        "answer": "PSU is a public state-related land-grant research university with campuses and facilities throughout Pennsylvania, USA. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/DualDegree.php"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the rank of Pennsylvania State University (PSU) in the QS World University Rankings of 2023?",
        "answer": "PSU is ranked 93rd in the QS World University Rankings of 2023. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/DualDegree.php"
      },
      {
        "question": "How is Nitte (Deemed to be University) rated in terms of accreditation and ranking?",
        "answer": "Nitte (Deemed to be University) is accredited by the National Assessment & Accreditation Council, Government of India with an 'A+' Grade and is ranked 65th in the National Institutional Ranking Framework (NIRF) of India in 2023. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/DualDegree.php"
      },
      {
        "question": "What opportunities does the Twinning Program provide for students?",
        "answer": "It offers an international learning environment, training in advanced laboratories, and opportunities to enhance cultural competence and networking for future career growth. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/DualDegree.php"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the objective of the Twinning Program?",
        "answer": "The objective is to provide students with the opportunity to study at a highly reputed American university and gain international exposure. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/DualDegree.php"
      },
      {
        "question": "How is the Twinning Program structured?",
        "answer": "It follows a model of 2+1+1, with students completing their third year at Penn State University, Harrisburg. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/DualDegree.php"
      },
      {
        "question": "What benefits do students receive by studying at Penn State University (PSU) under the Twinning Program?",
        "answer": "Students receive access to advanced laboratories, an international learning environment, and opportunities for networking and cultural competence enhancement. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/DualDegree.php"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the approval status of the Twinning Program?",
        "answer": "The Twinning Program has received approval from the All India Council for Technical Education (AICTE). For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/DualDegree.php"
      },
      {
        "question": "How are the credits earned by students at Penn State University, Harrisburg, recognized?",
        "answer": "The credits earned at PSU, Harrisburg, are recognized towards the degree requirements through a bipartite agreement between NitteDU and PSU. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/DualDegree.php"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the significance of completing the 3rd year at Penn State University, Harrisburg, in the Twinning program?",
        "answer": "It provides students with an opportunity to experience international education, gain exposure to different teaching methodologies, and enhance their academic and cultural competence. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/DualDegree.php"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the bipartite agreement between NitteDU and PSU entail?",
        "answer": "The bipartite agreement outlines the terms and conditions for credit transfer, ensuring that the credits earned at PSU are recognized by NitteDU towards the completion of the degree requirements. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/DualDegree.php"
      },
      {
        "question": "How does completing the 3rd year at PSU benefit students in terms of their academic and professional development?",
        "answer": "It allows students to access advanced facilities, engage with industry experts, and broaden their perspectives, enhancing their readiness for the global workforce. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/DualDegree.php"
      },
      {
        "question": "How are the credits earned at Penn State Harrisburg transferred back to NitteDU?",
        "answer": "The credits earned at Penn State Harrisburg are transferred back to NitteDU through the established partnership and agreement between the two institutions. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/DualDegree.php"
      },
      {
        "question": "What degree do students receive upon successfully completing the Twinning Program?",
        "answer": "Students who successfully complete the program receive a B.Tech in Computer Science Engineering from Nitte (Deemed to be University). For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/DualDegree.php"
      },
      {
        "question": "How does transferring to Penn State Harrisburg benefit NitteDU students in terms of academic and professional growth?",
        "answer": "Transferring to Penn State Harrisburg provides NitteDU students with access to advanced resources, internship opportunities, and a global learning environment, enhancing their academic and professional skills and preparing them for future career endeavors. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/DualDegree.php"
      },
      {
        "question": "How will the selection of candidates be made?",
        "answer": "Selection of candidates will be based on their academic performance. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/DualDegree.php"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the prerequisites for acceptance into the semesters of study at Penn State Harrisburg?",
        "answer": "Students must have earned a minimum of 80 credits by the end of the second year at Nitte with a cumulative grade point average (CGPA) of 6.25 on the Nitte Grading Scale, which is equivalent to 2.5 on the Penn State grading scale. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/DualDegree.php"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many credits are NitteDU students expected to complete upon transfer to Penn State Harrisburg for the third year?",
        "answer": "NitteDU students are expected to complete 65 credits during their third year at Penn State Harrisburg. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/DualDegree.php"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the program fee of this twinning program?",
        "answer": "For detailed program fee structure please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/btech_cse_twinningprogram.php"
      }
    ]
  }